Jester Hairston Collection MS040
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sound recordings unrelated to Jester Hairston, 1910 -- 1989; 1920 -- 1950; MS040.002; 25.2 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Crazy blues / It's right here for you, 1920; MS040.002.029.00011; Mamie Smith and her Jazz Hounds (Box 29)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Okeh 4169 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00002./
  - Crazy blues / It's right here for you, 1920; MS040.002.029.00012; Mamie Smith and her Jazz Hounds (Box 29)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Okeh 4169 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Deep river / Every mail day, 1946 -- 1950; MS040.002.029.00013; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 29)
  - Deep valley / Trombonology, 1947; MS040.002.029.00014; Tommy Dorsey and his orchestra (Box 29)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20-2419 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Diane / Over the mountain, 1949; MS040.002.029.00015; Simpkins, Arthur Lee (Box 29)
    Long Beach, CA./ Crystalette./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Crystalette no. CR 609./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Die walkure - ho - yo - to - ho / Allerseelen, 1950; MS040.002.029.00016; Flagstad, Kirsten (Box 29)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 1726 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Dus keshiniver shickele / Greena bletter, 1940; MS040.002.029.00017; Oysher, Moishe (Box 29)
    New York./ Banner./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Banner B 2083 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Easy go / But then you kissed me, 1950; MS040.002.029.00018; Stan Kenton and his orchestra (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Capitol./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Capitol 1191 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 002, MS040.002.026.00007./
  - Elijah / My trouble is hard, 1948; MS040.002.029.00019; Dixie-aires (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Exclusive./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./
  - Eve cost Adam just one bone / You'll never need a doctor no more, 1920; MS040.002.029.00020; Williams, Bert (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 3339 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Everybody wants a key to my cellar / It's nobody's business but my own, 1919; MS040.002.029.00021; Williams, Bert (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 2750 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Fedora / I pescatori di perle, 1929; MS040.002.030.00001; D'Alessio, Roberto (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Festival concert of choral music, 1950; MS040.002.030.00002; Capital Chorus (Box 30)
    Hollywood, CA./ Capital./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Includes original record jacket./
  - Gambia talk / Iron bar [sides 7 and 8], 1941 -- 1945; MS040.002.030.00003; Manning, Sam; Felix Krazy Cats (Box 30)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: West Indian Folk Songs, MS040.002.026.00005./
  - Go down Moses / Black sheep, where you left you' lamb [and] Little David, play on yo harp, 1950; MS040.002.030.00004; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 30)
    Chicago, IL./ Sonora./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: American Spirituals, MS040.002.026.00001./
  - Go down Moses / Black sheep, where you left you' lamb [and] Little David, play on yo harp, 1950; MS040.002.030.00005; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 30)
  - God's promise / There is a fountain, 1950; MS040.002.030.00006; Five Blind Boys of Alabama [Happyland Singers] (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty Shelf no. 876./
  - Go on about your bizness / Boggin' in the swamp, 1950; MS040.002.030.00007; Dick Taylor and his Taylor Made Music (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Webster./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Untitled record album 002, MS040.002.026.00007./
  - Guitar boogie / Mama blues, 1945; MS040.002.030.00008; Alvino Rey and his Orchestra (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Capitol./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Capitol 15223 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - He's a darn good man / Some day sweeheart, 1922; MS040.002.030.00009; Hunter, Alberta (Box 30)
    New York./ Black Swan./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Black Swan Shelf no. 2019./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - He's calling me / You must be born again, 1945; MS040.002.030.00010; The Original Gospel Harmonettes (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty Shelf no. 874./
  - Home, sweet home / The last rose of summer, 1930; MS040.002.030.00011; Maynor, Dorothy (Box 30)
    [United States]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 10-1340 (78A)./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Honey I don't want you / You foolish thing, 1951; MS040.002.030.00012; The Ravens (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 39408 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 002, MS040.002.026.00007./
  - I certainly was going some / Woddman, spare that tree, 1913; MS040.002.030.00013; Williams, Bert (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 1321 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - I'll be satisfied / After while, 1949; MS040.002.030.00014; Selah Singers (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Capitol./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Capital Shelf no. 70018./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./
  - I love to love / Love me or leave me, 1955; MS040.002.030.00015; Horne, Lena (Box 30)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20-6073 (78A)./
  - I'm gone before I go / The Lee family, 1916; MS040.002.030.00016; Williams, Bert (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 2078 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00002./
  - I'm gonna quit Saturday / My last dollar, 1920; MS040.002.030.00017; Williams, Bert (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 3356 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - I'm tired of everything but you / Best of all, 1925; MS040.002.030.00018; Morse, Lee (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Pathe./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Path 025155 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - I remember you / The breeze and I, 1951; MS040.002.030.00019; George Shearing Quintet (Box 30)
    [United States]./ MGM Records./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. M-G-M 10986 (78A)./
  - Italian street song / Summer serenade, 1935; MS040.002.030.00020; MacDonald, Jeanette (Box 30)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 10-1134 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - It's getting so you can't trust nobody / It's nobody's business but my own, 1920; MS040.002.030.00021; Williams, Bert (Box 30)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 35593 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - It's Mother's day (so wear a carnation) / The regular fellow's prayer, 1953; MS040.002.030.00022; The Bilbrew Quartet (Box 30)
    Los Angeles, CA./ Dootone./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Dootone Shelf no. 339./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - I've got my ticket in my hand / I know the Lord will make a way for me, 1950; MS040.002.031.00001; James, C.T. (Box 31)
    Los Angeles, CA./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ Shelf no. 1001./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./
  - I won't sell out / Just the name Jesus, 1954; MS040.002.031.00002; Professor Alex Bradford and The Bradford Specials (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty Shelf no. 865./
  - Jesus is a rock in a wearly land / Song of praise, 1953; MS040.002.031.00003; Five Blind Boys of Alabama [Happyland Singers] (Box 31)
    Houston, TX./ Peacock./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Peacock Shelf no. 1723./
  - Jesus gave me water / Peace in the valley, 1951; MS040.002.031.00004; The Soul Stirrers (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty Shelf no. 802./
  - Jesus is coming, 1947; MS040.002.031.00005; Lutcher, Joe (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Jordan Religious Series./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Jonah in the belly of the whale / With his stripes we are healed, 1927; MS040.002.031.00006; Rev. F. W. McGee and Congregation (Box 31)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20773 (78A)./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./
  - Just a closer walk with thee / Steal away, 1949; MS040.002.031.00007; Foley, Red (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 9-14505./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Just as soon as my feet strike Zion, Lord I won't be troubled no more / Adam and Eve in the garden, 1926; MS040.002.031.00008; Rev. J.M. Gates (Box 31)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20365 (78A)./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./
  - Just call his name / Lead me! Guide me!, 1945; MS040.002.031.00009; Brother Joe May and the Pilgrim Travelers (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Specialty SP 860 (78A)./
  - La fanciulla del west / Turandot, 1920; MS040.002.031.00010; Ziliani, Alessandro (Box 31)
    Italy./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Lakme-ou va la jeune indoue (Bell song) (Act 2) / Lakme-la bas, dans la foret (Bell song-concluded) (Act 2), 1935; MS040.002.031.00011; Pons, Lily (Box 31)
    [United States]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 1502 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Lay down your soul / Jezebel, 1925; MS040.002.031.00012; The Golden Eagles (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Federal./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./
  - Les fille de Cadix, 1920; MS040.002.031.00013; Galli-Curci, Amelita (Box 31)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 64885 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Lonesome alimony blues / Save a little dram for me, 1920; MS040.002.031.00014; Williams, Bert (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 2979 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00002./
  - Lonesome road / I'd like to know you better than I do, 1947; MS040.002.031.00015; The Commanders (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Modern Hollywood./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Modern Hollywood shelf no. 20-567./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Lord, I want to be there / Stay in touch with Jesus, 1947; MS040.002.031.00016; Henry, Reuben (Box 31)
    [United States]./ Fidelity./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Fildelity shelf no. 2001./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Lovin' Sam from Alabam / Don't care blues, 1920; MS040.002.031.00017; Mamie Smith and her Jazz Hounds (Box 31)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Okeh 4253 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Low down chariot / I'm singin' Hallelujia, 1940; MS040.002.031.00018; Southern Jubilee Quartet (Box 31)
    Linden, NJ./ DeLuxe./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Malaguena / Creole love call, 1944; MS040.002.032.00001; Adler, Larry (Box 32)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 24137./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Melody of love / None by the lonely heart, 1941; MS040.002.032.00002; Wayne King and his Orchestra (Box 32)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 27713 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Memphis blues / The Saint Louis blues, 1948; MS040.002.032.00003; Lanin's Southern Serenaders (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Hytone./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Hytone K 97 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Michigan water blues / Keeps on a-rainin', 1957; MS040.002.032.00004; Martin, Sara (Box 32)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Okeh Shelf no. 8060./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Minuet / Andante [sides 7 and 8 of 8], 1944; MS040.002.032.00005; Segovia, Andres (Box 32)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 24148./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - No man's momma / Shake that thing, 1925; MS040.002.032.00006; Ethel Waters and her Ebony Four (Box 32)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 14116 D (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - None but the lonely heart / The blind ploughman, 1925; MS040.002.032.00007; Gorin, Igor (Box 32)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 4436 (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Orare orare / Marara [sides 3 and 4], 1949; MS040.002.032.00008; Thurston Knudson-Augie Goupil and their Jungle Rhythmists (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 25437./ Record from album: Jungle Drums, MS040.002.026.00003./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - The old cross road (is waiting) / Remember the cross, 1947; MS040.002.032.00009; Bill Monroe and his Blue Grass Quartet (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Columbia Shelf no. 25437./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Papa don't want no fish and rice again / Go back to you ma [sides 1 and 2], 1941 -- 1945; MS040.002.032.00010; Manning, Sam; Felix Krazy Cats (Box 32)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 70009./ Record from album: West Indian folk songs, MS040.002.026.00005./
  - Parade of the wooden soldiers / By the waters of the Minnetonka, 1947; MS040.002.032.00011; Waters, Ethel (Box 32)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 24477./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Paradise blues / My syncopated melody man, 1916; MS040.002.032.00012; Harris, Marion (Box 32)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 18152 (78A)./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./
  - RCA Victor encyclopedia of recorded jazz [Album four - E to GAR], 1955; MS040.002.032.00013 (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Jazz Club of America./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Reckless blues / St. Louis blues, 1925; MS040.002.032.00014; Smith, Bessie; Armstrong, Louis (Box 32)
    London./ Parlophone./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Parlophone A 7500 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Reiterballade / Sonmerzeit, 1950; MS040.002.032.00015; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 32)
    Germany./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: American spirituals, MS040.002.026.00002./
  - Rhumba Uganda / Samba tembo [sides 5 and 6], 1949; MS040.002.032.00016; Thurston Knudson-Augie Goupil and their Jungle Rhythmists (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 25438./ Record from album: Jungle Drums, MS040.002.026.00003./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Rhythm rhapsody / Rhumba boogie, 1947; MS040.002.032.00017; Reyes, Chuy (Box 32)
    [United States]./ Capitol./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Capitol Shelf no. 15067./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Seeds of brotherhood, 1950; MS040.002.033.00001; Brotherhood Singers (Box 33)
    Hollywood, CA./ Brotherhood./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Sextette from Lucia, 1920; MS040.002.033.00002; Royal Marine Band of Italy (Box 33)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor Record./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Victor Shelf no. 2495./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Silent night / Velociter exaudi me, 1950; MS040.002.033.00003; Capella Sistina [Sistine Chapel Choir] (Box 33)
  - Since all is passing, 1956; MS040.002.033.00004; Redondo Union High School Madrigal Choir (Box 33)
    [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ This record appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Slipping on a banana peeling, 1950; MS040.002.033.00005; Johnny Lee & Elroy Peace (Box 33)
    [United States]./ Romeo Records./ 1 sound disc: 45rpm, 7-inch./
  - Some of these days / Louisville Lou (that vampin' lady), 1947; MS040.002.033.00006; Tucker, Sophie (Box 33)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 24289 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Someone loves someone / Ultra, 1947; MS040.002.033.00007; Harry James and his Orchestra (Box 33)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 38557 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Song of songs / Easter parade, 1947; MS040.002.033.00008; Como, Perry (Box 33)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20-2142 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - The stranger said / Sweet sugar cane, 1950; MS040.002.033.00009; The Voices of Walter Schumann (Box 33)
    Camden, NJ./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 45rpm, 7-inch./ Victor Shelf no. 47-6879./
  - Swanee river boogie / I don't want to see you, 1946; MS040.002.033.00010; Albert Ammons and his Rhythm Kings (Box 33)
    [United States]./ Mercury./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Mercury 70158 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Sweet kisses / They're all sweeties, 1919; MS040.002.033.00011; Van and Schenck (Box 33)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 2792 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Sweet Willie / Salt lane gal, 1941 -- 1945; MS040.002.033.00012; Manning, Sam; Felix Krazy Cats (Box 33)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 18258./ Record from album: West Indian Folk Songs, MS040.002.026.00005./
  - Tales of Hoffman - Barcarolle, 1914; MS040.002.033.00013; Homer, Louise; Gluck, Alma (Box 33)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Victor Shelf no. 87532./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - That sweet something dear / What could be sweeter dear, 1922; MS040.002.033.00014; Harvey, Georgia (Box 33)
    New York./ Black Swan./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Black Swan Shelf no. 14135./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Tico tico / (1) Lero lero (2) Bem te vi atrevido [sides 1 and 2 of 8], 1944; MS040.002.033.00015; Ethel Smith and the Bando Carioca (Box 33)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 23353 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Transeamus / White Christmas, 1950; MS040.002.033.00016; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 33)
    Germany./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Columbia Shelf no. 5351./ Record from album: American spirituals, MS040.002.026.00002./
  - Tu es Petrus / Justorum animae, 1950; MS040.002.033.00017; Capella Sistina [Sistine Chapel Choir] (Box 33)
    Los Angeles, CA./ Sunset Records./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Sistine Choir, MS040.002.026.00004./
  - Two black crows [parts 1 and 2], 1927; MS040.002.033.00018; Moran and Mack (Box 33)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 935 D (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Two black crows [parts 3 and 4], 1927; MS040.002.033.00019; Moran and Mack (Box 33)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 1094 D (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Two black crows [parts 5 and 6], 1927; MS040.002.033.00020; Moran and Mack (Box 33)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 1198 D (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Underworld blues / Caldonia blues, 1924; MS040.002.034.00001; Wallace, Sippie (Box 34)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Okeh 8144 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Use me Lord / Job and Satan, 1950; MS040.002.034.00002; The Trumpeteers (Box 34)
    [United States]./ Score Records./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Untitled record album 001, MS040.002.026.00006./
  - Water boy / Hear de lam's acryin' [and] Goin' to ride up in de chariot, 1950; MS040.002.034.00003; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 34)
    Chicago, IL./ Sonora./ 1 sound disc: 78rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: American Spirituals, MS040.002.026.00001./
  - Water boy / Hear de lam's acryin' [and] Goin' to ride up in de chariot, 1950; MS040.002.034.00004; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 34)